

SANTI TABBACH SSR REACT ENGINEER

/santiago-tabbach in

tabbach97@gmail.com



https://medium.com/@ymmhydfct



santitabbach.duckdns.org



ABOUT ME

Passionate SSR software engineer specializing in frontend development with experience in React and React Native. Currently contributing to implementation of new functionalities for a USA healthcare project. Simultaneously working on my thesis for software engineering degree.

MAIN SKILLS













Typescript

React

Redux

Jest

Figma

GitHub

SUPPORT SKILLS

- SOLID principles and Design Patterns
- Design Golden rules & Nielsen Heuristics
- Agile methodologies (SCRUM Kanban)
- Atlassian tools (Jira, confluence, etc)

MY PROJECTS

TripAdvisor for Restaurants (RN + Firebase)

Developed a mobile app for restaurant classification and reviews. Implemented real-time features using Firebase.

Garbage Classificator with IA (RN + Firebase)

Developed a mobile App for waste classification using an Al library. Integrated with Firebase for data storage and processing

Personal Finance Mobile App (RN + Firebase)

Developed a mobile app for personal finance management. Used Firebase for secure storage of financial data.

Incident Alert Mobile App (RN + TS + RTK Query)

Developed a mobile application to alert neighborhood residents about incidents, track them and generate reports for authorities.

EDUCATION

Software engineering

Universidad Tecnológica Nacional - FRVM 2018 - 2024

EXPERIENCE

SEMI SENIOR REACT ENGINEER

Intive

2023 - Present

Maintaining and developing new features for high quality software.

JUNIOR REACT ENGINEER

SimTLiX (now Intive)

2021 - 2023

Taking my first steps in my professional career as a developer, learning, and contributing to the team with a proactive attitude.

PREFERRED BOOKS

- Design patterns Alexander Shvets
- The design of everyday things Don Norman

A BIT MORE...

While I love frontend development, I also have a strong interest in and recognize the importance of UX/UI design. Currently, I am honing my skills in this area using Figma as a design tool and applying design patterns, Nielsen heuristics, Shneiderman's Golden Rules, among others.

I also acknowledge the significance of English in the software development industry. Therefore, I am working hard to enhance both my communication and comprehension skills in English.